[
  {
    "id": "33177",
    "question": "You may drive off the paved roadway to pass another vehicle:",
    "options": [
      "If the shoulder is wide enough to accommodate your vehicle.",
      "If the vehicle ahead of you is turning left.",
      "Under no circumstances."
    ],
    "answer": "Under no circumstances."
  },
  {
    "id": "23944",
    "question": "When approaching a railroad crossing with no warning device, the speed limit is:",
    "options": [
      "15 mph.",
      "20 mph.",
      "25 mph."
    ],
    "answer": "15 mph."
  },
  {
    "id": "32665",
    "question": "Parallel parking is when the:",
    "options": [
      "Front wheels are turned toward the street.",
      "Vehicle is in line with other parked vehicles.",
      "Rear wheels are touching the curb."
    ],
    "answer": "Vehicle is in line with other parked vehicles."
  },
  {
    "id": "18941",
    "question": "When you are merging onto the freeway, you should be driving:",
    "options": [
      "At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.",
      "5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.",
      "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway."
    ],
    "answer": "At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway."
  },
  {
    "id": "63859",
    "question": "Dim your high-beam headlights to low-beams within ______ feet when a vehicle is coming towards you.",
    "options": [
      "200",
      "300",
      "500"
    ],
    "answer": "500"
  },
  {
    "id": "29073",
    "question": "A blue curb means:",
    "options": [
      "Parking for mail delivery only.",
      "Parking for disabled persons with a special placard or license plate.",
      "Parking for disabled persons."
    ],
    "answer": "Parking for disabled persons with a special placard or license plate."
  },
  {
    "id": "33951",
    "question": "There is a school bus ahead of you in your lane with flashing yellow lights. You should:",
    "options": [
      "Stop, then proceed when you think all the children have exited the bus.",
      "Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously.",
      "Slow down and prepare to stop."
    ],
    "answer": "Slow down and prepare to stop."
  },
  {
    "id": "33084",
    "question": "California's \"Basic Speed Law\" says:",
    "options": [
      "You should never drive faster than posted speed limits.",
      "You should never drive faster than is safe for current conditions.",
      "The maximum speed limit in California is 70 mph on certain freeways."
    ],
    "answer": "You should never drive faster than is safe for current conditions."
  },
  {
    "id": "90928",
    "question": "You just sold your vehicle. You must notify ______ within 5 days.",
    "options": [
      "CHP",
      "DMV",
      "Your insurance provider"
    ],
    "answer": "DMV"
  },
  {
    "id": "28608",
    "question": "Looking down the road to where your vehicle will be in about 10 seconds helps you to ______________.",
    "options": [
      "Enjoy the scenery",
      "Avoid last minute moves",
      "See hazards inside your car"
    ],
    "answer": "Avoid last minute moves"
  },
  {
    "id": "55081",
    "question": "Which of these is not a pedestrian",
    "options": [
      "Bicyclist",
      "Disabled person using a wheelchair",
      "Blind person with a cane"
    ],
    "answer": "Bicyclist"
  },
  {
    "id": "89540",
    "question": "Which of the following statements about blind spots is true",
    "options": [
      "They are eliminated if you have one outside mirror on each side of the vehicle",
      "Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles",
      "Blind spots can be checked by looking in your rear-view mirrors"
    ],
    "answer": "Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles"
  },
  {
    "id": "27431",
    "question": "Which of these is considered a common cause of collision",
    "options": [
      "Unsafe speed",
      "Not following stop signs, signals, and signs",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All the above"
  },
  {
    "id": "28617",
    "question": "A person convicted of reckless driving or engaging in a speed contest that causes injury to another person is subject to",
    "options": [
      "Imprisonment and/or fine",
      "Community service",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Imprisonment and/or fine"
  },
  {
    "id": "18358",
    "question": "You may legally block an intersection",
    "options": [
      "When you entered the intersection on the green light",
      "During rush hour traffic",
      "Under no circumstances"
    ],
    "answer": "Under no circumstances"
  },
  {
    "id": "58393",
    "question": "When you park on a hill, your vehicle could roll due to an equipment failure. Remember to",
    "options": [
      "Leave the vehicle in neutral",
      "Set the parking brake",
      "Set the parking break and leave the vehicle in park"
    ],
    "answer": "Set the parking break and leave the vehicle in park"
  },
  {
    "id": "24026",
    "question": "With a Class C driver's license, a person may drive a",
    "options": [
      "Light rail train",
      "Car, van, or pick-up truck",
      "Semi-truck"
    ],
    "answer": "Car, van, or pick-up truck"
  },
  {
    "id": "64445",
    "question": "To turn left from a one-way street onto a one-way street, you should start your turn from",
    "options": [
      "Any lane",
      "The lane closest to the left curb",
      "The lane in the center of the road"
    ],
    "answer": "The lane closest to the left curb"
  },
  {
    "id": "17778",
    "question": "If you are involved in a traffic collision with property damage of $1000 or more, you are required to complete and submit a written report (SR1) to",
    "options": [
      "CHP",
      "DMV",
      "EDD"
    ],
    "answer": "DMV"
  },
  {
    "id": "27663",
    "question": "Roadways are least slippery",
    "options": [
      "On bridges in freezing temperatures",
      "After it has been raining for a while",
      "During the first rain after a dry spell"
    ],
    "answer": "After it has been raining for a while"
  },
  {
    "id": "80889",
    "question": "You may not park your vehicle:",
    "options": [
      "On the side of the freeway in an emergency.",
      "Next to a red painted curb.",
      "Within 100 feet of an elementary school."
    ],
    "answer": "Next to a red painted curb."
  },
  {
    "id": "19939",
    "question": "If you are involved in a traffic collision and no one is injured, you are required to complete and submit a written report (SR1) to:",
    "options": [
      "EDD.",
      "DMV.",
      "CHP."
    ],
    "answer": "DMV."
  },
  {
    "id": "21289",
    "question": "Treat lines as a barrier, when:",
    "options": [
      "Two sets of solid, double white lines are spaced two feet apart.",
      "Two sets of solid, double yellow lines are spaced two or more feet apart.",
      "Two sets of broken yellow lines are spaced one foot apart."
    ],
    "answer": "Two sets of solid, double yellow lines are spaced two or more feet apart."
  },
  {
    "id": "20855",
    "question": "You want to make a right turn at an upcoming intersection. You should slow down and:",
    "options": [
      "Move toward the left side of your lane.",
      "Avoid driving in the bicycle lane.",
      "Signal for 5 feet before turning."
    ],
    "answer": "Move toward the left side of your lane."
  },
  {
    "id": "15072",
    "question": "You are driving on a freeway and the posted speed limit is 65 mph. The traffic is traveling at 70 mph. You may legally drive:",
    "options": [
      "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.",
      "Between 65 mph and 70 mph.",
      "No faster than 65 mph."
    ],
    "answer": "No faster than 65 mph."
  },
  {
    "id": "20515",
    "question": "It is illegal to park your vehicle:",
    "options": [
      "In an unmarked crosswalk.",
      "Within three feet of a private driveway.",
      "In a bicycle lane."
    ],
    "answer": "In an unmarked crosswalk."
  },
  {
    "id": "13332",
    "question": "The safest precaution you can take regarding the use of cell phones and driving is:",
    "options": [
      "Only use your cell phone in hands-free mode when necessary.",
      "Keep your phone within easy reach so you will not need to take your eyes off the road.",
      "Review the number before answering a call."
    ],
    "answer": "Only use your cell phone in hands-free mode when necessary."
  },
  {
    "id": "13012",
    "question": "When is it safe to enter an intersection on a solid green light?",
    "options": [
      "When you can go around the traffic already in the intersection.",
      "When you have enough space to cross the intersection before the light turns red.",
      "When you cannot completely cross the intersection."
    ],
    "answer": "When you have enough space to cross the intersection before the light turns red."
  },
  {
    "id": "24404",
    "question": "You are getting ready to make a right turn. You should:",
    "options": [
      "Signal and turn immediately.",
      "Stop before entering the right lane and let all other traffic go first.",
      "Slow down or stop, look left-right-left, and make the turn when safe."
    ],
    "answer": "Slow down or stop, look left-right-left, and make the turn when safe."
  },
  {
    "id": "81811",
    "question": "You must obey instructions from school safety patrols or crossing guards:",
    "options": [
      "At all times.",
      "Only during school hours.",
      "Unless you do not see any children present."
    ],
    "answer": "At all times."
  }
]